Finding Aid for the Theodore Bikel Papers LSC.2321
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence and subject files, 1946-2012
  - Subseries 1.1: Chronological files, 1946-2002
    - AJC Convention 1982 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Arts International, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Arts organizations, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - General B, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Balkan Arts Center ethnic folk arts, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Debra Berger/ Project Interchange, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - General C, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Contracts completed, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Contract correspondence completed Jan-March, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Contract corres. completed April-June, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Contract correspondence completed July-September, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Contract correspondence completed October-December, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Chron, file Jan-June (letters sent), 1982 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Chron, file July-Dec. (letters sent), 1982 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - General D, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - General E, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Employment/ Theo, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - EBM/ Union Trust Theo account, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - EBM Hayes & Hume, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Ajax Rent A Car (EBM), 1982 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - EBM bills HHP, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - EBM checks HHP, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - EBM oil investments, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Personal F, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Fan mail/ autograph request, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - FIA conference Paris, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Film Artists & Associates Dick Heckenkamp, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - General G, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - General H, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - General I, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Inquiries - interviews, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries - movies & TV, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries - theatre, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries - concerts/ lectures, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries - good works, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 2-3)
    - Inquiries - panels/ conferences, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - JWB Lecture Bureau, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - General J, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - General K, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Kramer & Reiss, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - General L, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Personal M, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - General M, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Medical receipts, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Willaim Morris general correspondence, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - WMA/ Ed Robbins correspondence, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - WMA/ Greg Mullins correspondence, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - General N, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Personal N, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - NEA expense reimbursement, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - NEA general correspondence, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Remarks by Theo/ May mtg National Council/ NEA, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - NEA material, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - General O, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Orders placed, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Orders received, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Pan Continental Tours, Inc., 1982 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - General P, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Personal R, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - General S, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Schedules, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Tony Awards, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Wm. Takas correspondence, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Tay-Sachs, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - General T, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - General U, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Wormser, Heldfond, & Joseph, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - General W, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Personal Y, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - General Z, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Austria to 1983 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - General A, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Actors' Equity general correspondence, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Actors' Equity expense reimbursement, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - AFTRA, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - American Jewish Conference Governing Council, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - American Jewish Congress Executive Committee, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - General B, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - General C, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Contracts completed, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Contract correspondence completed January-March, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Contract correspondence completed April-June, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Contract correspondence completed July-September, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Contract correspondence completed October-December, 1983 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence file Jan-June (letters sent), 1983 (Box 148, Folder 2-3)
    - Correspondence file July-Dec (letters sent), 1983 (Box 148, Folder 4-5)
    - General D, 1983 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - General E, 1983 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - EBM - gen. corres., 1983 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - EBM - Hayes & Hume, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - EBM - tax record corres., 1983 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - EBM - bills - HHP, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - EBM - bills - Bikel, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - EBM - checks - Bikel, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - EBM - checks - HHP, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Deposits & correspondence EBM, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Ajax Rent-A-Car (EBM), 1983 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - EBM investments, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Warner Communications (EBM), 1983 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - ULLICO forms to be filed (Equity), 1983 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - ULLICO forms to Equity, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - ULLICo reimbursement, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - FIA, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Film Artists & Associates Dick Heckenkamp, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - General F, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - General G, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - General H, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - General I, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries good works, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries movies & TV, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries concerts/ lectures, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries auction requests, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries fan mail, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Invitations, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - General J, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - General K, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - General L, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - General M, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - WMA correspondence - general, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - General N, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - NEA correspondence, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - General O, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Orders placed, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Orders received, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - General P, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Pan Continental, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - General R, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - General S, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Schedules, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - General T, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - William Takas, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - General U, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - General V, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - General W, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - USA Cable/ Tele-Culture German shows, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - General X, Y, Z, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - (NEA subject files), 1977-1983 (Box 151, Folder 4-6, Box 152, Box 153, Folder 1-4)
    - Reading file - all correspondence (letters sent), 1984 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - (Letters sent), 1984 (Box 153, Folder 5-6)
    - AAdvantage FTC, 1981-1985 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - General A, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Personal A, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Actors' Equity General correspondence, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - AFTRA, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Actors' Equity expense reimbursement, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - American Jewish Congress Governing Council, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - American Jewish Congress Executive Committee, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - AJC/ Martin Steinberg Cntr., 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Associated Council on the Arts, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - General B, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Personal B, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - General C, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Personal C, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Contract correspondence completed Jan-May, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Contract correspondence, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Contracts completed, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Personal D, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - General D, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Personal E, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - General E, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - General F, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Personal F, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - FIA, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Personal G, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - General G, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Personal H, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - General H, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - General I, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Personal I, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries concerts/ lectures, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries & good works, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries - movies & TV, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries - fan mail, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries - auction requests, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - General K, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Personal K, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - General L, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Personal L, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - General M, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Personal M, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - General N, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Personal N, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - "Nuts", 1984 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - National Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - NEA correspondence, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Orders received, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - General O, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Personal O, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - General P, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Personal P, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania Stage Company stationery & envelopes, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Personal Q, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - General Q, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - General R, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Personal R, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - General S, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Personal S, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - SAG, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Seaboard Oil, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Smirnova, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Personal T, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - ULLICO reimbursement, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - General U, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Personal U, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - General V, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Personal V, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - William Takas, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - General W, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Personal W, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - General X, Y, Z, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Personal X, Y, Z, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Actors' Equity Association general correspondence, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - AEA - expenses, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - AFTRA, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - ACA (Associated Council on the Arts), 1985 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Personal B, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - General B, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - General C, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Personal C, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Contract corres. completed Jan.-June, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 2-3)
    - Contract corres. completed July-Dec., 1985 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Contracts completed, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Personal D, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - General D, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - General E, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Personal E, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - EBM - general corres., 1985 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - General F, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Elliot Finkel, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Personal F, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - FIA, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Personal G, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - General G, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Personal H, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - General H, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Personal I, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - General I, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries & good works, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries - concerts and lectures, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries fan mail, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - General J, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Personal J, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Personal K, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - General K, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Personal L, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - General L, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Personal M, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - General M, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - WMA - correspondence, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Personal N, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - General N, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Personal O, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - General O, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Orders received, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Orders placed, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Personal P, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - General P, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Pan Continental, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Personal Q, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - General Q, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Personal R, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - General R, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Personal S, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - General S, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - SAG forms to SAG, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Personal T, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - General T, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - General U, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Personal U, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - General V, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Personal V, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - General W, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - General XYZ, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - NEA correspondence, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Personal W, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Personal XYZ, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - (Legal records), 1986 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Actors' Equity, 1986 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Personal A, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - ACA, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - AFTRA, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - General B, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Personal B, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - General C, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Contracts completed, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Contract correspondence complete Jan/June, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 3-4)
    - Contract correspondence complete July/Dec, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - (Contract correspondence, letters sent), 1986 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - General D, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Personal D, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - General E, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - EBM general corres., 1986 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Ajax Rent A Car (EBM), 1986 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - EBM oil investments, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - General F, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Elliot Finkel, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - FIA, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - General G, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - General H, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Personal H, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - General I, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries good works, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Inquiries concerts and lectures, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Inquiries fan mail, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - General J, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - JWB correspondence, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Personal K, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - General K, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - General L, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Personal L, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - General M, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Personal M, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - WMA correspondence, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - General N, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Orders placed, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Orders received, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - General P, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - General R, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - General S, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - SAG, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - SAG to be filed, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - SAG forms to SAG, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - General T, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - General U, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - General V, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - General W, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - General XYZ, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - A general, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - A personal, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - ACA, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - AJC, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - AFTRA, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - B personal, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - B general, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - C personal, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - C general, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Contract corres. comp. (Jan.-June), 1987 (Box 160, Folder 2-3)
    - Contract corres. comp. (July-Dec.), 1987 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Contracts completed, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - D personal, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - D general, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - E personal, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - E general, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - EBM gen. cor., 1987 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - EBM investments, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Hayes & Hume, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - F personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - F general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Elliot Finkel, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - G personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - G general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - H personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - H general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - I personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - I general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries - good works, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries - concerts, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries - fans, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - J personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - J general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - K general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - L personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - L general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - M personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - M general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - N personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - N general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - O personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - O general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Orders placed, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Orders received, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - P personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - P general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Q personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Q general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - R personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - R general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - S personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - S general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - SAG, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - T personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - T general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - U general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - U personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - V personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - V general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - W personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - W general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - XYZ personal, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - XYZ general, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Daily planner, 1987 (Box 223, Folder 2-3)
    - (Appointment book/ notebook), 1985-1987 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - (Letters sent), 1988 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Contract corres. comp., 1988 (Box 161, Folder 7, Box 162, Folder 1-2)
    - Press clippings, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - A general, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - AEA, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - AFTRA, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - AJC, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - ACA, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - AEA election, 1988 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - B general, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - C general, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Contracts completed, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Checks Bikel, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Checks HHP, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - D general, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - E general, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Elliot Finkel, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - EBM oil investments, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - EBM investments, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - EBM gen. corres., 1988 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - F general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - G general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - H general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Hayes & Hume, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Tax record corres., 1988 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Bills Bikel, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Bills HHP, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - I general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries good works, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - K general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - J general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - L general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - M general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - N general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - O general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Orders received, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Orders placed, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Pan Continental, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Q general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - R general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - S general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - SAG, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - T general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - U general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - W general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - XYZ general, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - (Loose subject files: Israel & US Jewry), 1988 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Daily planner, 1988 (Box 223, Folder 4-5)
    - Planners, 1987-1989 (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - AEA (Actors' Equity Association), 1980s (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - ACA (American Council for the Arts), 1980s (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Associated Actors and Artistes of American (AFL-CIO), 1980s (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - FIA (Federation Internationale des Acteurs), 1970s (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - FIA (Federation Internationale des Acteurs), 1970s-1980s (Box 164)
    - FIA (Federation Internationale des Acteurs), 1980s (Box 165)
    - Misc. Corr., 1989 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Contract corres completed, 1990 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - (Concerts), 1990 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - (Concerts), 1990 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries, 1990 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - I, 1990 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries + good deeds, 1989-1990 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - G, 1990 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - NEA, 1990 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Trump (Trump Plaza reviews), 1990 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Give My Regards to Broadway, 1991 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Cleveland Opera, 1991 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Contracts completed, 1991 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Inquiries, 1991 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - WMA, 1991 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Austrian pension, 1991 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - P.R., 1989-1990 (Box 196, Folder 5-6)
    - P.R., 1990-1992 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Ariadne auf Naxos, 1992 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Fiddler on the Roof media kit, 1992 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Harrisburg 5/5/92, 1992 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Viennale, 1993 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Municipal Theatre Association, 1993 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Royalty statements, 1993 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Contract corres complete, 1993 (Box 197, Folder 4-5)
    - Concert corres, 1994 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Concert corres complete, 1993-1994 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Contracts completed, 1994 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - EBM checks, 1994 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - F, 1994 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Fiddler - box office statements, 1994 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - 1995 calendar (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Contracts, 1995 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Contract corres, 1995 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Contract corres completed, 1995 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Inquiries, 1996 (Box 198, Folder 5)